https://businessfinancearticles.org/privacy-policy

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footerEducationCareerInvestment & MoneyAccounting & TaxationTransportation & LogisticsIndustriesBusinessCommerceManagementInsuranceBanking FinanceMarketing & AdvertisingTechThis privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how Website Operator (“Website Operator”, “we”, “us” or “our”) collects, protects and uses the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you (“User”, “you” or “your”) may provide on the https://businessfinancearticles.org website and any of its products or services (collectively, “Website” or “Services”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.Collection of personal informationWe receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you create an account, publish content, fill any online forms on the Website. When required this information may include your email address, name, or other Personal Information. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Website’s features. Users who are uncertain about what information is mandatory are welcome to contact us.Collection of non-personal informationWhen you visit the Website our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. This data may include information such as your device’s IP address, browser type and version, operating system type and version, language preferences or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.Managing personal informationYou are able to access, add to, update and delete certain Personal Information about you. The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Website or Services change. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. Once the retention period expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of the retention period.Use and processing of collected informationAny of the information we collect from you may be used to personalize your experience; improve our Website; run and operate our Website and Services. Non-Personal Information collected is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding Website usage. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.We may process Personal Information related to you if one of the following applies: (i) You have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note that under some legislations we may be allowed to process information until you object to such processing (by opting out), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases below. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Information is subject to European data protection law; (ii) Provision of information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof; (ii) Processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which you are subject; (iv) Processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in us; (v) Processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. In any case, we will be happy to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.Information transfer and storageDepending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring and storing your information in a country other than your own. You are entitled to learn about the legal basis of information transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by us to safeguard your information. If any such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with us using the information provided in the contact section.The rights of usersYou may exercise certain rights regarding your information processed by us. In particular, you have the right to do the following: (i) you have the right to withdraw consent where you have previously given your consent to the processing of your information; (ii) you have the right to object to the processing of your information if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent; (iii) you have the right to learn if information is being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the information undergoing processing; (iv) you have the right to verify the accuracy of your information and ask for it to be updated or corrected; (v) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of your information, in which case, we will not process your information for any purpose other than storing it; (vi) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information from us; (vii) you have the right to receive your information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that your information is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on a contract which you are part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.The right to object to processingWhere Personal Information is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in us or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, you may object to such processing by providing a ground related to your particular situation to justify the objection. You must know that, however, should your Personal Information be processed for direct marketing purposes, you can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether we are processing Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you may refer to the relevant sections of this document.How to exercise these rightsAny requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.Privacy of childrenWe do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through our Website or Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through our Website or Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us through our Website or Service, please contact us.CookiesThe Website uses “cookies” to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. We may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to operate our Website and Services. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the Website and Services.What Are CookiesAs is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or ‘break’ certain elements of the sites functionality.For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies.How We Use CookiesWe use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.Disabling CookiesYou can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.The Cookies We SetAccount related cookiesIf you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.Login related cookiesWe use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.Third Party CookiesIn some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.The Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.For more information on Google AdSense see the official Google AdSense privacy FAQ.More InformationHopefully that has clarified things for you and as was previously mentioned if there is something that you aren’t sure whether you need or not it’s usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site.However if you are still looking for more information then you can contact us through one of our preferred contact methods:AdvertisementWe may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our customers that we collect through the registration process or through online surveys and promotions with certain advertisers. We do not share personally identifiable information about individual customers with advertisers. In some instances, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements to the intended audience.Links to other websitesOur Website contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites or third-parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that may collect Personal Information.Information securityWe secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal Information in its control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and our Website cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third-party, despite best efforts.Data breachIn the event we become aware that the security of the Website has been compromised or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third-parties as a result of external activity, including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. In the event of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law. When we do we will post a notice on the Website, send you an email.Changes and amendmentsWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy relating to the Website or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Policy on the Website. When we do we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. Continued use of the Website after any such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes.Acceptance of this policyYou acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By using the Website or its Services you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to use or access the Website and its Services.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Policy, please contact usThis document was last updated on May 25, 2018Primary SidebarSearch this website
Are you often overwhelmed by your assignments and can't … [Read More...] about Tips To Keep In Mind While Handling Your College AssignmentSocial media has taken the world by storm. It has … [Read More...] about Your Professional Spotlight: The Right Approach to Marketing Your Skills on LinkedInPlanning to start new business is strenuous unless you … [Read More...] about Low Risk Business Ventures to Start TodayBefore knowing the procedure of starting the investment … [Read More...] about How to Start an Investment PartnershipStruggling to start your own dog treat brand, but … [Read More...] about How to Start your Dog Treat Business?Video marketing is an essential component of Internet … [Read More...] about How to Expand Your Brand with Corporate Video Production in Sydney?Transportation businesses require a little bit more … [Read More...] about 3 Tips to Establish a Transportation BusinessThe current financial market has numerous lenders … [Read More...] about Is Fullerton Personal Loan a Good Option?Credit cards have emerged as one of the best payment … [Read More...] about Essential Tips for Students Using Credit CardNot very long ago, the major problem for companies was … [Read More...] about Why is Cloud Computing Important?Spotify is a premium music streaming and audio content … [Read More...] about Safe ways to buy Spotify followersMany people today want to have their own business. … [Read More...] about Should You Start a Business When You Have Debt?Business is all about taking chances. It is the best … [Read More...] about How To Run A Business Successfully- Revealing Top-Notch Approaches To AdoptA strategic study plan, the right approach, and SBI PO … [Read More...] about Best Preparation Strategies for SBI PO 2020One of the most important things that can have an … [Read More...] about A Brief Guide to Life Insurance for Police EmployeesEvery country in the world has needy or poor people. In … [Read More...] about Difference between Grant and DonationPoor cash flow is the top reason why businesses fail, … [Read More...] about 3 Ways to Make Sure Your Company’s Finances Are SecureAs an entrepreneur or business person, the last thing … [Read More...] about Protecting Your Business and EmployeesIn this modern era, the fourth industrial revolution is … [Read More...] about Emerging Career Trends in Different PathwaysDuring the COVID-19 pandemic, many businesses have … [Read More...] about Funding Solutions for Businesses During the COVID-19 PandemicMost ViewedBusiness Growth Business Ideas Business Needs Business Tips Career Advice Career Development Career Guide Career Options COVID-19 Credit Card credit card reviews Credit Score Debt Management Differences Employee Entrepreneurship HRM Import-Export Importance Investment Loan Provider Loans MCQs Online Marketing Organization Pakistan Partnership Past Papers Payday Loan Payday Loans PPSC Production Pros Cons Publicity Quick Money Tips Roles and Duties Startups Strategies Students Help Tips Top10 Types UK UK Banks USARecent CommentsMariya Amjad on Low Risk Business Ventures to Start TodayJignesh Patel on PPSC MCQs: Curriculum DevelopmentGeorge on Hiring a Commercial Electrician in SydneyImran khan on PPSC MCQs: The Muslim of the Subcontinent & Their Educationiqra on PPSC MCQs: The Muslim of the Subcontinent & Their Education.M.Arif on PPSC MCQs: Curriculum DevelopmentAmna on Low Risk Business Ventures to Start TodayQuratulain Merchant on What to know before hiring someone on Freelance PlatformsQuratulain Merchant on How to Build a Strong Brand Image?Quratulain Merchant on Why Do Managers Micromanage?
FooterAbout USContact UsBlogComment PolicyTerms & ConditionsPrivacy RightsPrivacy PolicyFollow on Google NewsFollow on FacebookFollow on TwitterFollow on MediumEntrepreneur SkillsBusiness CycleBusiness IdeasSpeculatorBe WealthyPsychology in HRMHRM in BusinessBusinessman QualitiesSalespeople TypesHealth & BusinessBusiness Success RulesStress At Work
